internetsecure.com 2004-12-23

# InternetSecure Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy** This document explains InternetSecure Inc.’s (“InternetSecure”) policies for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. 

This policy forms part of, and should be read in conjunction with, our 

_**Terms of Use**_. 

InternetSecure believes that privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of Internet commerce. Our status as an Internet merchant account provider and certified payment gateway requires us to have a stringent policy regarding all of the information that we collect. 

Your use of this site or InternetSecure’s services constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions. If you do not agree with these policies, please cease using this site immediately. 

These terms were last revised on April 19, 2004. InternetSecure reserves the right to amend these policies from time to time. If such amendments affect how InternetSecure uses or discloses personal information already held by InternetSecure in a material and adverse way over and above previous express or implied consent, InternetSecure will contact you to obtain consent. Notwithstanding the terms of this policy, the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information may be made outside of the terms herein to the extent provided for in the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, and other relevant Canadian and Ontario legislation in effect from time to time. These exemptions include, without limitation, publicly available information, or information disclosed for criminal or civil investigations or compliance with law or court orders. 

InternetSecure takes reasonable precautions to ensure your privacy on the terms contained in this policy. InternetSecure uses reasonable efforts to, but cannot totally prevent, unintended disclosures by such means as hackers and other unauthorized individuals, and inadvertent or illicit employee actions. 

**Cardholder provided Information:**

Our electronic purchase service requires that cardholders provide contact information (including without limitation: name, address, city, state or province, postal code, country, telephone and email), and financial information (including without limitation: name on credit card, credit card number and expiry date), and ordering information. This information is collected and used to process the transaction and for internal accounting and other procedures. Following a transaction, we may contact cardholders by phone or email for security purposes. 

**Merchant Provided Information:**

Our site’s merchant application form requires merchant applicants to provide contact information (including without limitation: company name, contact name, address, city, province, country, postal code, telephone number, fax number, email address and website address), financial information (including without limitation: GST number, PST number, merchant number, transit number and discount rate, and banking information) and general business information (including without limitation business type, social insurance number, years in business, principles of organisation, delivery type, description of products and/or services and minimum & maximum transaction amounts). 

We use information collected from the merchant to send the merchant information about InternetSecure, to contact the merchant for various reasons, and for internal accounting and other procedures. Information is used to check the merchant’s eligibility for our service and to obtain and verify further information from financial institutions and credit reporting agencies or bureaus in regard to the application, and to support the ongoing provision of service. Such information may be provided to such third parties for those purposes. It is also used for login validation purposes. 

**Information Automatically Collected:**

Our Web site keeps track of usage data, such as the source address that a page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the referring Web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. The IP addresses we collect on our electronic purchase service are linked to personally identifiable information. This is collected in order to combat fraud during the purchase process. We also use this data to better understand Web site usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of our Web site users prefer. Automatically collected information is also used for the same purposes as cardholder supplied and merchant supplied information. 

**Sharing of Information:**

Certain information submitted through the electronic purchase service (excluding credit card numbers) is shared with the merchant from whom the cardholder is purchasing the products / services so the merchant can fulfill the order. Information is also shared with other parties necessary to complete credit card transactions, including, without limitation, companies related to InternetSecure, credit card companies, credit card clearing houses and processors, and financial institutions. 

InternetSecure is acting as an intermediary between the merchant and a user’s credit card company. The parties mentioned in the above paragraph, and not InternetSecure, are responsible for their own privacy polices and for maintaining privacy and confidentiality for all information InternetSecure provides them. If a user has any questions or concerns about the privacy policies of those parties, it must contact such parties. 

Except for the above parties, and for use by InternetSecure’s consultants and professional advisers on InternetSecure’s behalf for the uses disclosed herein, InternetSecure does not share personal information with any other third parties. InternetSecure may, however, provide to third parties aggregate or statistical information that does not disclose personally identifiable information. InternetSecure may disclose personal information to another entity purchasing (including for diligence purposes prior to purchase) the assets of InternetSecure, providing that entity abides by this or a similar privacy policy. 

**Contact Us / Email Inquiries:**

No information sent to InternetSecure via email or the website inquiry form is used for any other reason than to respond to and maintain a record of the inquiry. This information is not sent to third parties or retained for mailing list purposes. 

**Security:**

InternetSecure takes measures to protect and keep information secure. Our Merchants’ area, application form and electronic purchase service are secured with SSL encryption. Verisign has supplied us with digital certificates for our Web sites. All information collected by InternetSecure is held offline, secured via SSL encryption, and protected by a firewall. Whenever sensitive information is transmitted to InternetSecure through our Web site, such as a credit card number, our server provides 128-bit encryption of the information as it travels across the Internet. InternetSecure restricts internal access to personal information to selected members of InternetSecure’s staff. 

**Third Party Dispute Resolution:**

InternetSecure Inc. is committed to resolving disputes quickly and efficiently. In the event that a dispute cannot be settled through our normal internal processes, InternetSecure Inc. is committed to using an independent third party dispute resolution process. 

This process can be initiated through [ ThirdPartyResolution@internetsecure.com](mailto:ThirdPartyResolution@internetsecure.com) only after our normal internal processes have been completed. 

In the event the issue relates to private information, InternetSecure Inc. will not use or distribute any private information without express permission. All disputes in arbitration will be resolved under the laws of Ontario. 

**Opt out / Correct / Update:**

This site gives Merchants the following options for removing their information from our database to cancel future communications, to no longer receive our service, or to change their information on our database: 

1\. send email to [service@internetsecure.com](mailto:service@internetsecure.com)   
2\. call the following telephone number inside North America: 1-800-297-9482.  
3\. call the following telephone number outside North America: +001-905-469-6522.

**Contacting InternetSecure:**

If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this web site, you may contact: 

InternetSecure Inc.  
2201 Speers Road  
Oakville ON  
L6L 2X9  
Phone: (800) 297-9482  
Fax: (905) 469-6560  
Email: [service@internetsecure.com](mailto:service@internetsecure.com)
